Evelyn Bankell

September 05, 1997

1 +46 73 980 94 20

@ evelyn@bankell.se

• Current Location : Holtermansgatan 3D, Göteborg i Portfolio: https://evelynbankell.github.io/

in linkedin.com/in/evelynbankell



I am a fifth-year student in Media technology, which is an education with an emphasis on technology, where the foundation is a solid foundation in mathematics, physics, programming and information technology. I am specialized in areas such as full stack web development, information visualization, user interface and interaction between humans and technology. I am currently doing my Master Thesis at Filmgate in Gothenburg within front-end development and information visualization.



Education

2016-Present MSc. in Media technology and Engineering, Linköping University

Télécom SudParis, Computer Science 2019-2020

Exchange year in France



Professional Experience

Warehouse work, Biltema Logistics, Summer of 2019

Worked as a terminal worker.

Full stack web developer, Jayway by Devoteam, Summer of 2018

Worked with maintenance of internal web systems for project and resource planning, developed in Ruby

on Rails.

Summer of 2017 Waitress, Wapnö,

Worked as a waitress serving breakfasts and dinners.

Shop assistant, Östras Stenugnsbageri, 2013-2016

Worked weekends, summers and holidays as a shop assistant and cashier at a bakery, as well as with wa-

rehouse work.

Gymnastic Leader, Söndrums Gymnastik- och Idrottsförening, 2012-2016

Worked as a gymnastics leader for children between the ages 3-6 once a week.



Volunteer Experience

Web developer, Sofia's Sömnad

Created the website sofiassomnad.se, using React.js.

2015, 2017 Conference assistant, Øredev Developer Conference

Worked in the reception, wardrobe and at the information desk.



Swedish (native) Languages:

English (fluent) French (intermediate)

Programming: C++, Java, Javascript/NodeJS, HTML5, CSS, Matlab, Python, Ruby on Rails

Frameworks: React.js, React Native, Redux, Express, pygame Databases: Google Data Store, SQL, MongoDB, Neo4j

> Cloud: GCP, AWS

Other: Git, npm, API design, REST, JSON, Google Authentication, OpenGL, Autodesk 3ds Max, Maya,

Unity

Portfolio: https://evelynbankell.github.io/